### Contact

azeronas@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angelazeronas-bsn-ccrn-22779045 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare

**BLS** 

Patient Advocacy

### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

# Angela Zeronas BSN, CCRN

CVICU travel RN at Fastaff Travel Nursing

Youngstown, Ohio Area

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Coaching, Medical Devices, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Emergency Medicine, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a bachlor of science focused in nursing from Penn State University.

## Experience

Fastaff Travel Nursing
CVICU RN travel
January 2020 - Present (6 months)
Bronx, New York

Faststaff
Travel RN
2015 - Present (5 years)

Sharon Regional Health System
Registered Nurse
May 2002 - Present (18 years 2 months)
cardiothoracic intensive care

ProLink Staffing
Travel CVICU RN
June 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 8 months)

UPMC Horizon Shift Supervisor April 2013 - March 2015 (2 years) Greenville/Shenango, PA

St. Elizabeth's Hospital Registered Nurse

July 2012 - March 2014 (1 year 9 months) CVICU/SICU

## Education

Penn State University bachlor of science, nursing · (2000 - 2003)

Youngstown State University undergraduate, Chemistry